A Guide to the Russell Gregg Photograph Collection, ca. 1920-1944
Thomas Balch Library
Thomas Balch Library
Russell Gregg Photograph Collection ca. 1920-1944
Thomas Balch Library
VC 0008
This collection consists of 715 photographs taken by Russell Gregg of Loudoun County and its residents during the 1920s, 1930s, and the early 1940s
Russell Gregg
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection open for research.
Acquisition Information
Mary Gregg Reynolds, Ossining, NY
Alternative Form Available
Digital surrogates
Accruals
2000.0003
Biographical Information
Russell Gregg was born on April 6, 1890 to Edgar Bentley and Mary Nichols Gregg at his family farm west of Hamilton, Virginia. He worked as a farmer with his brother while becoming an amateur photographer. He worked for the Loudoun Times-Mirror as a photographer, specializing in high school classes. He married Anne Pierce in October of 1917; they did not have any children. For the last few years of his life, Gregg lived with his niece, Mary Gregg Pancoast Reynolds. He died on December 16, 1980 in Purcellville, Virginia.
Loudoun County in the 1920s, 1930s, and 1940s had a stable population of approximately 20,000 people. The county was predominately agricultural, with more than 2000 farms in 1920. In 1920-1921, Loudoun was negatively impacted by the stabilization of Europe after World War I, which had previously depended on America farms for food and goods. By 1922, prices had returned to pre-war levels, and dairy became a large part of Loudoun's economy. The W&OD Railroad influenced the growth of industry in Loudoun, as well as the continued support of the dairy market. Loudoun County was not immediately affected by the stock market crash in 1928; the drought of 1930 brought the Great Depression to Loudoun. Most relief was provided by the Virginia Department of Agriculture, but the number of farms dropped below 1700. The Rural Electrification Administration brought electricity to Loudoun in 1935, making domestic and agricultural work easier. World War II brought about a revival to the economy, as Loudoun farms and industries were once again needed to support the war effort. In addition to supporting the war at home, 3000 Loudoun men signed up for the draft before the age limit was lowered from 21 to 18 years. Fifty-one of those men died in the war.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of 715 photographs taken by Russell Gregg of Loudoun County and its residents during the 1920s, 1930s, and the early 1940s. They include wedding pictures, family portraits, individual portraits, as well has pictures of houses, groups, and events in Loudoun County. The bulk of the photographs are of high school students: graduates, sports teams, and classes.
Most of the collection was digitized in 2004, after which the negatives were discarded. Print sizes are primarily 4"x6", 5"x7" and 8"x10". Photographs are organized by date, and then alphabetically according to content. Undated images are organized at the beginning of the collection. Physical photographs are organized according to size, and by catalogue number.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Bibliography
History of Loudoun County. www.loudoun.gov/Default.aspx?tabid=1123
Leesburg, Virginia: An Exploration through History (DVD). Town of Leesburg, 2010.
Poland, Charles P. From Frontier to Suburbia: Loudoun County, Virginia. Westminster, Maryland: Heritage Books, 2005.
"Russell Gregg, 90, Dies Farmer, Photographer." Loudoun Times-Mirror Dec 18, 1980: A 18.
"Mrs Russell Gregg, 88, Active in Church, Clubs." Loudoun Times-Mirror Nov 20, 1969: A 14.
Other Finding Aid
Past Perfect catalogue records
Technical Requirements
Electronic media
Related Material
Leesburg May Pole Dance, 1932 (VC 0012), Thomas Balch Library, Leesburg, VA.
Contents List
- (VC 0008, ca. 1920-1944: 136 photographs arranged by size and chronologically, catalogued in Past Perfect, Thomas Balch Library's visual collections database.)
  - Folder 1
    - [Aldie High School], 5 x 7"
    - [Fairfax Volunteer Fire Co Baseball Team], 7 x 10"
    - [Leesburg High School Baseball Team], 4 x 6"
    - [Leesburg High School Basketball Team - Coach Caleb Gibson], 5 x 7"
    - [Leesburg High School Basketball Team - Coach Caleb Gibson], 4 x 6"
    - [Leesburg High School], 1935 ca., 9 x 14"
    - [Lincoln High School Football Team], 4 x 6"
    - [Lincoln High School Football Team], 4 x 6"
    - [Lincoln High School Graduates], 4 x 6"
    - [Lincoln High School Graduates], 4 x 6"
    - [Lincoln High School Students], 4 x 6"
    - [Lincoln High School girls - Sandy Speare], 5 x 7"
    - [Lincoln High School], 5 x 7"
    - [Lincoln High School], 4 x 6"
    - [Lucketts School Boys Basketball Team], 5 x 7", 4" x 4.5"
    - [Lucketts School Boys], 4 x 6"
    - [Lucketts School Children], 4 x 6"
    - [Lucketts School Girls Baseball Team], 4 x 6"
    - [Lucketts School Students], 4 x 6"
    - [Lucketts School Students], 4 x 6"
    - [Lucketts School Students], 4 x 6"
    - [Lucketts School], 4 x 6"
    - [Lincoln High School 1930] 4 x 6", 5" x 7", 1930
    - [Kenworthy House Interior Room] 4 x 6", 1930 ca
  - Folder 2
    - [Kenworthy House] 4 x 6", 1930 ca
    - [Kenworthy House] 4 x 6", 1930 ca
    - [Kenworthy House] 4 x 6", 1930 ca
    - [Kenworthy House 4 x 6", 1930 ca
    - [Kenworthy House] 4 x 6", 1930 ca
    - [Kenworthy House] 4 x 6", 1930 ca
    - [Kenworthy House] 3 x 5", 1930 ca
    - [Round Hill High School Graduate Kathleen Reid] 4 x 6", 1930 ca
    - [Round Hill High School Graduate] 4 x 6", 1930 ca
    - [Round Hill High School Graduate] 4 x 6", 1930 ca
    - [Round Hill High School Graduate] 4 x 6", 1930 ca
    - [Round Hill High School Graduate] 4 x 6", 1930 ca
    - [Lincoln High School Girls Basketball Team] 5 x 7", 1930s ca
    - [Round Hill High School Graduates] 5 x 7", 1930s ca
    - [Lincoln High School Football team 1934] 7 x 10", 1934
    - [Lincoln School - unidentified man] 5 x 7", 1934
    - [Lincoln High School 1935 Graduates] 4 x 6", 7" x 10", 1935
    - [Round Hill High School Baseball Team] 4 x 6", 1935 ca
    - [Hamilton Elementary School Students] 6.5 x 10", 1936
    - [Hamilton Elementary School Students] 4.5 x 7", 1936
    - [Hamilton Elementary School Students] 4 x 6", 1936
  - Folder 3
    - [Lincoln High School 1936 Graduates] 4 x 6", 7" x 10", 1936
    - [Lincoln High School Basketball] 4 x 6", 1936
    - [Lincoln High School Basketball] 5 x 7", 1936
    - [Lincoln High School Girls Basketball Team] 5 x 7", 1936
    - [Round Hill High School 1936 Graduates] 5 x 7", 4" x 6", 1936
    - [Round Hill School Tom Thumb Wedding] 4 x 6", 1936
    - [Aldie High School Girls Basketball team 1938] 4 x 6", 1937
    - [Leesburg High School] 4 x 6", 1937
    - [Lincoln High School 1937 Graduates] 7 x 10", 1937
    - [Lincoln High School 1937] 4 x 6", 7" x 10", 1937
    - [Lincoln High School Basketball] 5 x 7", 1937
    - [Lincoln High School Boys Basketball Team] 5 x 7", 1937
    - [Lincoln High School Football Team] 4 x 6", 1937
    - [Lincoln High School Football Team] 4 x 6", 1937
    - [Lincoln High School Track Teams] 7 x 10", 1937
    - [May Day on Emancipation Grounds - Crepe Paper Dresses Hamilton School] 8.5 x 11", 1937
    - [May Day on Emancipation Grounds - Hamilton School] 8.5 x 11", 1937
    - [Purcellville Elementary School] 4 x 6", 1937
    - [Purcellville Elementary School] 5 x 7", 1937
    - [Round Hill High School 1937 Graduates] 4 x 6", 1937
  - Folder 4
    - [Lincoln High School Basketball Teams] 5 x 7", 7" x 9", 1937 ca
    - [Round Hill High School Students with Teacher Frances Whitman] 4 x 6", 5" x 7", 1937 ca
    - [Aldie High School 1938 Boys Basket Ball Team] 5 x 7", 4" x 6", 1938
    - [Aldie High School 1938 Graduates] 4 x 6", 1938
    - [Aldie High School Girls Basketball team 1938] 5 x 7", 1938
    - [Leesburg High School] 4 x 6", 1938
    - [Lincoln High School 1938 Graduates] 7 x 10", 1938
    - [Lincoln High School 1938] 4 x 6", 5" x 7", 1938
    - [Lucketts School Students] 4 x 6", 1938
    - [Lucketts School Students] 5 x 7", 1938
    - [Purcellville Elementary School Baseball Team] 4 x 6", 1938
    - [Purcellville baseball team] 4 x 6", 1938
    - [Aldie High School 1939 Girls Basket Ball Team] 4 x 6", 1939
    - [Leesburg High School] 5 x 7", 1939
    - [Leesburg High School] 5 x 7", 1939
    - [Lincoln High School 1939 Teachers] 5 x 7", 1939
    - [Lincoln High School Boys Football Team] 4 x 6", 1939
  - Folder 5
    - [Lincoln High School Football Team] 4 x 6", 1939
    - [Lincoln High School Graduates] 5 x 7", 7" x 10", 1939
    - [Purcellville School 1939] 5 x 7", 1939
    - [Purcellville School Baseball Team 1939] 4 x 6", 5" x 7", 1939
    - [Round Hill High School 1939 Graduates] 5 x 7", 1939
    - [Round Hill Chorus] 5 x 7", 1939 ca.
    - [Teacher Alice Graiger (back left) with students presenting Easter Cantada] 4 x 6", 1939 ca.
    - [Aldie High School 1940 Boys Basket Ball Team] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Aldie High School 1940 Boys Basket Ball Team] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Leesburg High School] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Lincoln High School 1940] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Lincoln High School 1940] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Lincoln High School Students] 4 x 6", 1940
    - [Purcellville School 1940] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Purcellville School 1940] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Round Hill School Graduates] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Leesburg High School Graduates] 4 x 6", 1940 ca.
    - [Leesburg High School Graduates] 7 x 10", 1940 ca.
    - [Lincoln High School Band] 5 x 7", 1940 ca.
    - [Lincoln High School Football Team] 4 x 6", 1940 ca.
    - [Lincoln High School] 5 x 7", 1940 ca.
    - [Purcellville School] 4 x 6", 5" x 7", 1941
  - Folder 6
    - [Lincoln High School 1942 Graduates] 5 x 7", 1942
    - [Purcellville School] 4 x 6", 1942
    - [Lincoln High School 1943] 5 x 7", 7" x 10", 1943
    - [Lincoln High School Graduation - 1493] 8.5 x 11", 1943
    - [Lincoln High School 1944 Graduates] 5 x 7", 1944
    - [Lincoln High School Boys Basketball] 5 x 7", 1944
    - [Lincoln High School Football team 1944] 5 x 7", 1944
    - [Lincoln High School Girls Basketball Team] 4 x 6", 1944
    - [Lincoln High School Yearbook Staff] 5 x 7", 1939
    - [Round Hill School Faculty] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Round Hill School Band Members] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Round Hill School Baseball Team] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Round Hill School] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Round Hill School 1st and 2nd Grades] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Round Hill School 3rd and 4th Grades] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Round Hill School 5th and 6th Grades] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Round Hill School 7th and 8th Grades] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Round Hill School Freshman Class] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Round Hill School Sophomore Class] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Round Hill School Junior Class] 5 x 7", 1940
    - [Lincoln School in 1940s] 7 x 10", 1940 ca.
    - [Lincoln High School - 1938] 7 x 10", 1938
    - [Joe Lacey Children] 8 x 10", 1936
    - [Lucketts School Class picture - 1933] 8 x 10", 1933
- (Box vc_0008_0128 Leesburg High School, 9" x 14")
- (Digital)
  - Digital Surrogates, ca. 1920-1944
    vc_0008_0001 through vc_0008_0663
  - [Ambrose and Clifton Warner family]
  - [Ambrose and Cliff Warner family]
  - [Andrew C Norman]
  - [Anna Brouch Nichols wedding]
  - [Anna Brouch Nichols wedding]
  - [Ardi Newton family]
  - [Ardi Newton family]
  - [Ardi Newton]
  - [Arnie Vandeventer child]
  - [Ashburn High School Baseball Team]
  - [Ashburn High School Class]
  - [Ashburn High School Class]
  - [Ashburn High School Gym Class]
  - [Ashburn High School]
  - [Ashburn High School]
  - [Ashburn High School]
  - [Ashburn High School]
  - [Ashburn High School]
  - [Ashburn High School]
  - [Ashburn High School]
  - [Barn]
  - [Beacon Hill House]
  - [Boy Scout Leaders]
  - [Boy Scouts]
  - [Boy Scouts]
  - [Boy Scouts]
  - [Bus Trip]
  - [C Hough]
  - [Chain Bridge]
  - [Chamblin Steele Esso Station]
  - [Church group]
  - [Church]
  - [Claude Hornicon]
  - [Colonial Highway - Hamilton]
  - [Dorothy Hansbarger and baby]
  - [Dr Frazier family]
  - [Dr Frazier family]
  - [Dr Kerr house]
  - [Earl Whitman]
  - [Edgar Robey House]
  - [Elsea Girls]
  - [Evergreen Home - Hoge]
  - [Evergreen Home - Hoge]
  - [Football Team]
  - [Future Farmers of America - Ashburn High School]
  - [G. W. Hume Home - front]
  - [G. W. Hume Home - rear]
  - [Girl Scouts]
  - [Gordon Chamblin house]
  - [Gordon Chamblin house]
  - [Hamilton Post Office Picture of a Picture]
  - [Harry Filler]
  - [Harvey Ball House]
  - [Helen Walsh children]
  - [Helen Walsh children]
  - [Henry Taylor wedding]
  - [Herndon family]
  - [Herndon family]
  - [Herndon family]
  - [Herndon family]
  - [High School Graduation]
  - [Hilda Grubb and child]
  - [Home Demonstration]
  - [Home Demonstration]
  - [Home Demonstration]
  - [Home Demonstration]
  - [Home Demonstration]
  - [Home Demonstration]
  - [Home Demonstration]
  - [Home Demonstration]
  - [Home Demonstration]
  - [Hope Family]
  - [Hope Family]
  - [Hope Family]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [House]
  - [Houses]
  - [Howard Hoge House]
  - [Howard Hoge House]
  - [Howard Hoge Portrait]
  - [Howard Hoge Portrait]
  - [Howard Hoge Portrait]
  - [Howard Rogers]
  - [Howard and Sarah Hoge Family]
  - [Hugh Tillett]
  - [Hutchinson Chevrolet]
  - [Hutchinson Chevrolet]
  - [Isaac Ballinger]
  - [Ivy Hall]
  - [Jenkins Family - Harry and Arthur Jenkins]
  - [Jenkins Family - Harry and Arthur Jenkins]
  - [Jenkins Family - Harry and Arthur Jenkins]
  - [Joe Norman Children]
  - [John Divine]
  - [John Hansbarger baby]
  - [John Monroe Casket]
  - [John Monroe Grave Site]
  - [John Monroe House]
  - [Kasper Place]
  - [Kasper Place]
  - [Ketoctin Baptist Church]
  - [Ladies Group]
  - [Lakeland reunion]
  - [Lakeland]
  - [Lawrence Taylor]
  - [Leesburg Boy Scouts]
  - [Leigh]
  - [Linden McDaniel - baby]
  - [Love Farm]
  - [Lovettsville High School]
  - [Lovettsville High School]
  - [Lunaford Ladies]
  - [Margaret James]
  - [Martha Brown wedding]
  - [Mary Louise Laycock]
  - [May Day]
  - [May Day]
  - [May Day]
  - [Melbourne Family]
  - [Melbourne]
  - [Methodist Church - Reverend Moore]
  - [Methodist Church Choir]
  - [Methodist Church Ladies Group]
  - [Millie Ann Brown]
  - [Miss Tillett]
  - [Mr Cole family]
  - [Mr Laycock's son]
  - [Mr Laycock]
  - [Mr Lurlner]
  - [Mr Morris family]
  - [Mr Murnam House]
  - [Mr. Tillett]
  - [Mr. Warner]
  - [Mr. Weaning]
  - [Mr. Ritacor]
  - [Mr. Welsh]
  - [Mr. and Mrs. Flippo]
  - [Mr. and Mrs. Saunders]
  - [Mrs Harry Filler]
  - [Mrs Louis Titus]
  - [Mrs McGavick and child]
  - [Mrs McGavick child]
  - [Mrs McGavick family]
  - [Mrs McGavick house]
  - [Mrs Tillett]
  - [Mrs Weaning baby]
  - [Mrs. Arnie Vandeventer]
  - [Mrs. Arnold Pfieffer and baby]
  - [Mrs. Arnold Pfieffer - child]
  - [Mrs. Clarence Robey]
  - [Mrs. D Davis House]
  - [Mrs. D Davis Children]
  - [Mrs. Downs and baby]
  - [Mrs. Downs]
  - [Mrs. E Moffett Anniversary]
  - [Mrs. E Moffett Family]
  - [Mrs. E Moffett Family]
  - [Mrs. E Moffett]
  - [Mrs. Hayes Nichols's daughter - graduation]
  - [Mrs. Hayes Nichols's daughter]
  - [Mrs. Kenworthy - Ladies Group]
  - [Mrs. Samuel Rhodes Anniversary]
  - [Mrs. Samuel Rhodes family]
  - [Mrs. Samuel Rhodes family]
  - [Mrs. Welsh]
  - [Muriel Cornwell]
  - [Neilsen House]
  - [Pancoast Corn Field]
  - [Purcellville baseball team]
  - [Rob Reed Family]
  - [Rob Reed House]
  - [Robey House Garden]
  - [Robey House Garden]
  - [Robey House]
  - [Russell Thompson family]
  - [Sali Dowdell Confederate Money]
  - [Sara and Harry Tribby]
  - [Sara and Harry Tribby]
  - [Sletta Lurks House]
  - [Thomas Holmes and family]
  - [Thomas Holmes Family]
  - [Thomas Holmes baby]
  - [Unidentified Baby]
  - [Unidentified Baby]
  - [Unidentified People]
  - [unidentified woman]
  - [Unidentified Woman and car]
  - [Unidentified baby]
  - [Unidentified boy]
  - [Unidentified child]
  - [Unidentified house]
  - [Unidentified men]
  - [Unidentified men]
  - [Unidentified school]
  - [V. M. Workman baby]
  - [V. M. Workman family]
  - [W Everett Family]
  - [W Everett House]
  - [Walter Simpson and horse]
  - [Warner family]
  - [Warner family]
  - [Warner house]
  - [Wayside Market - Overlook Orchard]
  - [Wayside Market - overlook orchard]
  - [Wayside Market]
  - [Wedding - Mary Ann Nichols]
  - [Welsh Family]
  - [Welsh Family]
  - [Welsh House]
  - [Will Francis dog]
  - [Will Francis family]
  - [Will Francis family]
  - [Willard Silcott family]
  - [William Cockerille family]
  - [Yakey Family]
  - [Yakey Wedding]
  - [Yakey Wedding]
  - [unidentified baby]
  - [William Rhoden enlistment papers], 1913
  - [William Rhoden discharge papers], 1920
  - [Ross Bob - family group on porch], 1929
  - [Ross Bob - family group under Christmas Tree], 1929
  - [Ross Bob - four generations], 1929
  - [Arnold Grove Cemetary], 1930 ca.
  - [Arnold Grove Church], 1930 ca.
  - [Ivandale Florist delivery truck], 1930 ca.
  - [Ivandale Florist], 1930 ca.
  - [Ivandale Florist], 1930 ca.
  - [Ivandale Florist], 1930 ca.
  - [Wayside Inn - Dr Coffee Shop], 1930 ca.
  - [Gas stations at Loudoun & East Market Streets], 1930s
  - [St. James Episcopal Church], 1930s
  - [St. James Episcopal Church], 1930s
  - [Hamilton School], 1932
  - [Hillsboro School], 1932
  - [Lincoln High School Boys Basketball], 1933
  - [Lincoln High School Girls Basketball], 1933
  - [Lincoln High School Graduates], 1933
  - [Lincoln High School Graduates], 1933
  - [Lucketts School Class Picture], 1933
  - [Lucketts School Girls Basketball Team], 1933
  - [New Jerusalem Church], 1933
  - [New Jerusalem Church], 1933
  - [Purcellville school], 1933
  - [Purcellville school], 1933
  - [Purcellville school], 1933
  - [Upperville Church], 1933
  - [Upperville Church], 1933
  - [Purcellville school], 1935
  - [Miss Sarah Love], 1935 ca.
  - [Miss Sarah Love], 1935 ca.
  - [Lincoln School Football Team], 1936
  - [Morven Park turkey], 1936
  - [Morven Park], 1936
  - [Patsy Ely, George Richmond Ely, unidentified child], 1936
  - [Round Hill High School], 1936
  - [Tom Thumb Wedding], 1936
  - [Tom Thumb Wedding], 1936
  - [4-H Fair, Cows], 1937
  - [4-H Fair], 1937
  - [Aldie High School Boys Basketball Team], 1937
  - [Aldie High School Girls Championship Basketball Team], 1937
  - [Aldie High School Students], 1937
  - [Aldie High School Students], 1937
  - [Brunswick Bridge], 1937
  - [Court Complex], 1937
  - [Leesburg Baseball Team], 1937
  - [Leesburg High School], 1937
  - [Lincoln High School Girls Basketball Team], 1937
  - [Lincoln High School], 1937
  - [Lincoln High School], 1937
  - [Lincoln High School], 1937
  - [Lincoln High School], 1937
  - [Lincoln High School], 1937
  - [Lincoln High School], 1937
  - [Loudoun Court House], 1937
  - [Loudoun Hospital], 1937
  - [Lucketts High School Baseball Team], 1937
  - [Lucketts High School Students], 1937
  - [Morven Park - Westmoreland Davis], 1937
  - [Mrs Peyton and baby], 1937
  - [Noland House - Aldie Mill], 1937
  - [Peoples National Bank], 1937
  - [Peyton baby], 1937
  - [Radio Program - Oliver and Eli Myers], 1937
  - [Round Hill High School Student], 1937
  - [Round Hill High School Student], 1937
  - [Round Hill High School Student], 1937
  - [Round Hill High School Student], 1937
  - [Round Hill High School Student], 1937
  - [Round Hill High School Student], 1937
  - [Round Hill High School Student], 1937
  - [Round Hill High School Student], 1937
  - [Round Hill High School Student],v 1937
  - [Round Hill High School Student], 1937
  - [Round Hill High School Student], 1937
  - [Round Hill High School Students], 1937
  - [Round Hill High School Students], 1937
  - [Round Hill High School Students], 1937
  - [Schooley Family - two unidentified women], 1937
  - [Schooley Family - unidentified woman], 1937
  - [Sinclair Garage], 1937
  - [Tribby Baby], 1937
  - [Tribby Children], 1937
  - [Tribby Family], 1937
  - [Tribby Son], 1937
  - [Waterford School Baseball Team], 1937
  - [Waterford School Student], 1937
  - [Waterford School Student], 1937
  - [Waterford School Student], 1937
  - [Waterford School Students], 1937
  - [Waterford School Students], 1937
  - [Waterford School Students], 1937
  - [Waterford School Students], 1937
  - [Waterford School Students], 1937
  - [Waterford School Students], 1937
  - [Waterford School Students], 1937
  - [Waterford School Students], 1937
  - [Waterford School Students], 1937
  - [Waterford School Students], 1937
  - [Waterford School Students], 1937
  - [Waterford School Students], 1937
  - [Waterford School Students], 1937
  - [Waterford School], 1937
  - [W & OD Railroad Car], 1938
  - [Aldie High School], 1938
  - [Hillsboro School], 1938
  - [Leesburg Baseball Team - 1938], 1938
  - [Leesburg Baseball Team - 1938], 1938
  - [Leesburg Fire Truck 1938], 1938
  - [Leesburg Fire Truck 1938], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School Band], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School Football], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School Girls Baseball], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School Girls Baseball], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School Graduates], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School Teachers], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School], 1938
  - [Leesburg High School], 1938
  - [Lincoln High School Basketball Team], 1938
  - [Lincoln High School Football Team], 1938
  - [Lynn Cornwell and family], 1938
  - [Mr. and Mrs. Cornwell], 1938
  - [Mrs. Joe Nichols and baby], 1938
  - [Music Festival], 1938
  - [Music Festival], 1938
  - [Purcellville Golf Course Swimming Lessons], 1938
  - [Purcellville Golf Course], 1938
  - [Roger Anderson children], 1938
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1938
  - [Round Hill School Chorus], 1938
  - [St Peters Church], 1938
  - [WCTU], 1938
  - [WCTU], 1938
  - [WCTU], 1938
  - [unidentified house], 1938
  - [Aldie High School], 1939
  - [Aldie High School], 1939
  - [Aldie High School], 1939
  - [Aldie High School], 1939
  - [Aldie High School], 1939
  - [Carrico Wedding family], 1939
  - [Carrico Wedding], 1939
  - [Carrico Wedding], 1939
  - [Dave Edmondson], 1939
  - [Dorothea Erbe wedding], 1939
  - [Dr Musgrove's family - unidentified woman], 1939
  - [Dr Musgrove's family], 1939
  - [Dr Musgrove's house], 1939
  - [Leesburg High School Boys Basketball Team], 1939
  - [Leesburg High School Boys Basketball Team], 1939
  - [Leesburg High School Boys Football Team], 1939
  - [Leesburg High School Boys Football Team], 1939
  - [Leesburg High School], 1939
  - [Leesburg High School], 1939
  - [Leesburg High School], 1939
  - [Leesburg High School], 1939
  - [Leesburg High School], 1939
  - [Leesburg High School], 1939
  - [Leesburg High School], 1939
  - [Leesburg High School], 1939
  - [Lincoln High School Baseball Team], 1939
  - [Lincoln High School Girls and Boys Basketball Team], 1939
  - [Lincoln High School], 1939
  - [Lincoln High School], 1939
  - [Lincoln High School], 1939
  - [Lincoln High School], 1939
  - [Lincoln High School], 1939
  - [Lincoln High School], 1939
  - [Loudoun County High School Band], 1939
  - [Lula Neal wedding], 1939
  - [Mrs. Walsh Horses], 1939
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates], 1939
  - [Round Hill High School Graduates]
  - [Aldie High School]
  - [Aldie High School]
  - [Aldie School], 1940
  - [John Hansbarger and family], 1940
  - [Leesburg High School Baseball Team], 1940
  - [Leesburg High School Football Team], 1940
  - [Leesburg High School Girls Basketball Team], 1940
  - [Leesburg High School Parade], 1940
  - [Lincoln High School Basketball Team], 1940